Greetings folks, how's it going with you?
大家好啊，最近如何啊
It's going fine here, I suppose,
我这里还好吧
but I am very much missing going out
但我还是很想出去看看
and physically thrifting like I used to.
然后像以前一样淘点二手
It's just not a routine that I'm doing anymore
只不过我有一段时间没有
for the time being.
出去淘了
In fact, I haven't really gone out thrifting
实际上，我自从上回出去淘二手以来
注：av328822088 LGR Thrifts Ep.45 @ Superbart
since the last episode of LGR Thrifts.
基本就没出去过
And yeah, it's a bummer, but
是啊，这就很惨:-(
it's just kind of the reality of things at the moment.
但是呢，现在形势就是这样，咱也没办法:-|
A lot of stores are open, you know,
你也看见了，现在好多店也都开门了
but it's just not quite the same at the moment.
但我总感觉没有以前那味了
Things are still a little weird and
现在感觉还是很怪，所以
I pretty much go out for necessities
我现在也就在买日用品
and a coffee every so often.
和咖啡时出去
That's about it.
大约就是这样了
So that's that, but at the same time,
情况就是如此了，但是与此同时呢
that's not stopped me from thrifting, so to speak.
要我说，没有什么能阻止我去淘二手
I still do, you know,
你也懂得，我现在也在淘二手
online shopping and looking around for bargains
在网上淘些二手便宜货
and not-bargains,
或是不便宜的稀奇玩意
just interesting things on different websites,
就是在各大网站上卖的稀奇货
including Goodwill's.
包括Goodwill
So why not do a little bit of that today
所以要不现在咱就干吧
with something I'm calling eThrifts?
咱们将其称为eThrifts（线上淘二手）
Because that's a word now.
因为这样它就是一个词了
I know it won't be the same,
我知道这个感觉和亲自去不一样
you don't really find the type of bargains
你自己亲自出去淘二手
you do in person out in the wild,
一般淘不着啥好货
but let's do it anyway,
但是咱还是干吧
let's go eThrifting.
咱们来线上淘二手
线上淘二手系列
LGR
第一集
All right, so first up today is a Goodwill,
好的，今天咱们从GoodWill开始
or really the Shop Goodwill auction website.
更准确地说，是Shop GoodWill拍卖网
And in case you didn't know, Goodwills around the country
我来科普一下，全国的GoodWill
will often post interesting things,
经常把一些有意思的东西
or not-so-interesting things
或是那些没啥意思的东西
up for auction online instead of selling them in the store.
上传到网上，而不是在线下零售
Or sometimes they do sell them in the store
有时他们将东西同时
and also sell them online.
放在线上，或线下卖
You can either buy them in the store itself or
你可以在商店里直接买
yeah, just go online and try your luck at bidding.
或者跑网上参与竞价，看看你的运气如何
But you can find all sorts of randomness.
但是呢，你在网上啥东西都能看见
Like look at this, it just popped up randomly here,
你看看，它们就是这样随机地推送过来
bulk lot of Dell desktops.
比如这堆戴尔的台式机
Working lot of 20 for 98.99 at the moment.
20台能用的，目前叫价99.89美元
There are no bidders.
但是没人竞价
It's a pickup only thing.
这些东西都是甩卖货
Goodwill of Central & Northern Arizona? Okay.
等会，要到亚利桑那中北部的GoodWill店提货.......好吧
You get a lot of different bulk lots like this,
你经常会看见这些论堆卖的货
just sort of groups of things or collections of things
就像这样，将很多东西放在一起卖
that would be kind of awkward to sell in the store.
这些东西要是放在店里卖，有点不太合适
Then we got categories that are divided up into,
现在我们看到了目录，也就是这些
you know, things you'd normally find at Goodwill.
你懂的，你经常在GoodWill里看到的东西
There's a whole section for just religious items.
这里还有一些宗教物品
Cause you know, Goodwill's got a lot of that.
因为你也知道，GoodWill净是这些东西
Glassware, bulk.
玻璃制品啊，成堆卖的物件啊
Anyway, let's just look at some individual items.
无论如何，咱来看看一些具体物件
So yeah, I just typed in a search for vintage computer here.
好的，我刚才把“复古电脑”几个大字打入了搜索框
You never know what that'll find and
你永远也不知道你会在这里看见什么
what do you know?
你再来瞧瞧
An Apple III popped up.
这个Apple III电脑
I did not expect that!
这价我可真是没想到
Bids are already at 900-some dollars.
竞价都已经超过了900美元
I mean, go figure.
要我说，咱得看看
This thing looks basically brand new, unused.
这电脑看上去还真新，还没用过呢
I mean seriously clean, great condition,
真的是很干净，品相超级的好
256K memory model,
256K内存的型号
and apparently located at a Seattle Goodwill.
而且很明显是在西雅图的GoodWill店
That makes sense.
这很合理
If you know anything about the area,
如果你稍微了解一点这个区域的话
all sorts of interesting computery things
你就会知道，很多有趣的关于电脑的事情
can often come from there.
经常能在这里看到
And just kind of browsing around here in the gaming,
然后你再看看这些游戏
I found a lot of 16 assorted Atari video game cartridges.
我找到了16个分好的雅达利游戏卡带
It's already at $250
目前已经250美元了
so I'm assuming that this UltraVision's Condor Attack
所以我猜这个是UltraVision做的Condor Attack
注：这个是将10英寸彩色电视机，视频游戏系统和大功率计算机集成到一个单元中，所以失败了
is what's setting that price so high because
怪不得价格如此的高
none of these other carts are anything rare.
剩下的卡带就没有那么稀少了
Hmm, now this is a lovely looking receiver here.
嗯，现在咱来看看这个功放
Check this out, a Pioneer SX-780.
看看这个先锋SX-780功放
45 Watts per channel, already over $200.
每个声道是45瓦，目前竞价已经超过200美元了
This thing looks great.
品相看上去还不错
Just from that era that I really enjoy of receivers.
在那是，我可是耐死功放了
And got that black-backed VU meters
还有这个深邃黑暗的幻想表头
and FM tuner needle there, it's just so cool.
还有FM广播调频指针，这就很好
The wood grain's in good shape too.
这上面的木纹成色看上去也不错
A lot of times these are pretty beat up,
我看见过好多，都是破旧的
but this one looks pretty nice.
但是这个看上去品相十分的好啊
Oh wow, check this out.
哇，看看这个
That's a Marantz Superscope PSD300.
这是个 Marantz Superscope PSD300
This is a little portable field recorder,
这个小玩意是实地录音机
注：你可以理解成将录音机扔在野外哪个小角落中，让其自己录音
but it records to CDs, not cassettes.
但是它将音频录到CD中，而不是磁带
I first learned about this on Techmoan,
我是看了Techmoan的视频才知道这个的
I believe he covered this a couple of years ago
我确信他好像前几年
on his YouTube channel.
在他的Youtube上讲过
It's a fascinating looking design.
看上去品相不错
And yeah, I just liked the fact that it's a
而且呢，我喜欢它只是因为
portable CD recorder.
它是个便携式CD录音机
That's just neat.
就挺好
Ooh, check this out.
Woo，瞧瞧这个
We got a Commodore CRT monitor over here from 1988.
这是台1988年生产的Commodore牌显像管显示器
Of course, missing the front door.
当然，前挡板没了
They're always missing that front panel.
这种电视经常会丢失前挡板
Yeah, neat little monitor there.
但是呢，显示器还是不错的
1802, that would go nicely with a C64C or 128.
1802, 和C64C和128搭配一定很好
Oh man, check this out.
喔，看这玩意
This is a Apple Mac.
这是个 Apple Mac
This is a Mac Plus one megabyte model.
这是台 Mac Plus，1MB 内存版本
I've always wanted one of these in particular,
我一直都想要一个
Like I have a 128 and SE and such,
我就有一个 128 和 SE 之类的
but there's something about the plus.
但这个 Mac Plus 和那些有些不同
I don't know, maybe it's the Vaporwavy side, but I just...
我不知道在那吸引我了，也许是外观（没看懂），但是
It's appealing to me?
这品相行吗？
This one's unevenly yellowed, but that could be addressed.
这个表面发黄程度深浅不一，但是我只要化身漂白王就行了
It's only 35 bucks out of a Goodwill in Kansas.
这个在Kansas的Goodwill只卖35美元
I'm sure those bids will go up.
我相信竞价迟早会上去的
Oh, hey, I haven't seen one of these at a Goodwill yet.
嘿，我之前从来没有在Goodwill看见过这个
Online or in-person, there's a little NES Mini
无论是线上还是线下，这是个NES Mini
and it's only going for 7.99 currently.
目前报价仅仅是7.99美元
There's no bids on it.
目前没人报价
I can't say that I think it'll stay that way,
我无法保证价格会一直是这个数
somebody's bound to grab it.
很可能有人会最后开高价得到它
But yeah, 7.99, Goodwill of North Georgia.
再说一遍，7.99美元，货物在Georgia北的GoodWill店
Doesn't have the packaging of course, but it is tested
外包装自然是没有的，但是所有功能都
and it functions, more than you can usually say
被测试过了，和你们经常在商店里
for one in the store.
看到的是不一样的
Wow, you know, this is not normally my thing, but
你们知道这个不是我的菜，但是
the price just stood out.
这个价格让其脱颖而出
It's a 14 to 18 carat yellow gold charm bracelet.
这是个14K到18K的金制吊坠手环
$3,500 is the current bid.
目前竞价3500美元
注：2020年9月美国纽约黄金平均价为1940美元每盎司，约合68美元每克
这个是32美元每克
108 grams.
108克
I mean, yeah, check it out.
你来看看
They got the price of gold.
他们真是赚足了便宜
I have no doubt that a lot of people go to Goodwill
显然很多人去Goodwill
just snapping up gold or whatever.
只是匆匆地买到黄金就走
Maybe for scrap.
或者是淘点垃圾
I never really thought thought about it that much, but
我从来没有在这个问题想过太多，但是
yeah, why not, right?
为何不呢，对吧
A lot of people do it with old computer parts.
很多人用他们的老电脑部件来搞这些
Oh man, check out these speakers.
哇，看看这些扬声器
Not only the wood grain, but just like the overall designs.
不仅上面有木纹，总体看上去也很不错
They're JBL C38 floor speakers.
它们是 JBL C38 落地扬声器
And look at those connections.
再看看这些接口
When were these made?
哪里生产的呢？
I don't know, but James B. Lansing Sound, Incorporated.
我不知道，上面写着James B. Lansing Sound, Incorporated
I don't know, I love those speakers.
算了，这玩意耐人就对了
I would totally use those.
我十分想有一个
What is this?
这又是个嘛?
Three Game Boy ASCII Showcase System game cases?
三个 Game Boy ASCII Showcase System 游戏盒
Dude, this is awesome.
老兄，这玩意可耐人了
It's like a full on storage rack,
这可是一整个存储架呀
display thing for your Game Boy carts.
把你买的Game Boy卡带都码好，并展示出来
I've never seen those before and it's made by,
我以前从来都没有看到过，这个是
yeah, ASCII.
嗯，ASCII生产的
They did all sorts of different
他们是专门生产
peripherals and accessories and things but,
各种配件，附件之类的吧
yeah, I guess maybe these aren't too common.
但我觉得这个没有那么好找
$452 is the current price.
目前售价452美元
Ah man, what is this?
天哪，这堆东西是啥
I was just attracted to the picture
看上去就足够吸引眼球了
because of all the yellow.
因为这些黄色的
1960s Aurora Model Motoring.
1960s Aurora 汽车模型
That's like a really cool,
看上去超级酷的
it was a little slot car racetrack thing.
这个还有一些汽车轨道之类的
Man, you know, I've seen these kinds of things
我曾经在另外的Goodwill店里
at different Goodwills, just sort of tossed together
看见过这个，就是这样
in a big old cardboard box, but
打包在一个又大又破的纸箱中
typically they don't have any of the packaging,
但通常来说这个不会有这种包装的
much less so many things all in one.
而且没有这样一整套的
This is really neat for, you know,
这对于收藏这个的人来说，你懂的
the right type of collector.
确实是不错的
I don't know, I just still think it's pretty awesome.
谁知道呢，我觉得这个挺好的
$430 currently.
目前售价430美元
It's a Goodwill in Colorado,
目前在Colorado的Goodwill
seven hours remaining on this one.
目前还有7个小时结束竞价
Check out this lot of N64 goodness.
再看看这些关于N64的好东西
Not the greatest wheel in the world, but hey, whatever.
不是最好的
Nintendo 64. Good stuff.
Nintendo 64啊，是个好玩意
Perfect Dark, Duke 64, Banjo-Kazooie,
注：这些都是游戏，我就不翻译了
Hexen, Turok, Shadows of the Empire, Doom 64, Cruis'n,
like seriously.
诸如这些
I love pretty much all of these.
大多数我都爱玩
421 bucks at the moment.
目前售价421美元
Huh, this is a little different.
然后呢，这个有点特别
You got an autographed print with apparently
你可以搞到张签过名的照片
certificate of authenticity.
显然是有证书认证的
I mean, I guess that's real?
我是说，这玩意应该是真的吧
259 of 388.
388份中的第259份
Why 388?
为啥非得限量388份？
Such an arbitrary number.
真是够随意的:-P
Anyway, autograph crap.
无论如何，就是张签名
On the flip side of things being autographed,
在签名的另一面呢
"O Jerusalem," Triple Signed Print by Greg Olson.
是Greg Olson的三重签名版画作《耶路撒冷》
Pretty sure I've seen that picture in a
我绝对在很多地方的教堂里看过这个了
fair number of churches over the years.
Nobody's bidding on it and there's seven hours left.
目前没人竞标，还剩下七个小时
Welp.
好吧......
Here we go, I'm sure this is going to get
看看这个，我确信这个将会抓住某些人的眼球
some folks' attention.
Six and a half pounds of Pokemon trading cards.
六磅半的口袋妖怪交易卡
I don't really know much about these,
我对这些真的不太了解，
注：既然你们诚心诚意的问了，那我就大发慈悲地告诉你......:-P
but hey, look at that.
但是呢，仔细看看
They've got the thing there,
里面一大摞的卡片呢
just so you know it is indeed six and a half pounds.
看上去确实是六磅半
I believe it, look at all those stacked in there.
应该是的，看看里面放的这些卡片
Are these worth the price?
这个真值那么多钱吗
I don't know.
我不知道
Going for 256 bucks currently.
目前要价256美元
Goodwill Retail Services. What the heck is that?
Goodwill零售服务，那是什么呀？
They're apparently in Wisconsin, okay.
他们显然在威斯康星州，好吧......
Why it's listed as Goodwill Retail Services?
为什么将其列为“Goodwill零售服务”？
Hey, what in the world?
嗯，这是个啥情况？
They've got an iMac as well.
这里有台iMac
The old G4 here, is that the same one in Wisconsin?
二手G4，也在威斯康星吗
Looks, you know, decent.
看上去品相不错
I like how they marked off all the information
我很喜欢他们在底部打铭牌的方式
at the bottom here.
49 bucks, nobody's bidding on it so far.
49美元，到目前为止，没有人出价
Aw, poor Mac.
为他默哀一下吧:-)
I guess now Goodwill is showing me Pokemon
我很确信Goodwill又给我来个口袋妖怪
cause look at this, it brings up a
看看这个，它给我推荐了
Dark Charizard Holo Team Rocket.
Dark Charizard Holo Team Rocket
注：机翻都不知道是什么......
It's just one card, $250.
这只是一张卡，250美元
So I guess Goodwill knew what they were doing.
所以我想Goodwill知道他们在做什么
This particular Goodwill,
至少是这个Goodwill
just posting it on its own instead of part of the lot.
只是一张一张发布而不是全部发布
Shout out to the employee in Pennsylvania
必须批评一下宾州的Goodwill员工
who knew to list this.
这到底是谁列的？
Well, this is interesting.
好吧，这很有趣
Or at least it could be, but there's no photos really.
至少看上去是这样的，但实际上没有多少照片
15 movie posters, $231 currently,
15张电影海报，目前价格为231美元
but this is the only photo.
但这是唯一的展示照片
Ha! What the crap?
哈！这是个嘛玩意？
What else does it come with? Let's see here.
还有什么呢？让我们看看这里
So this is in Ohio.
这是在俄亥俄州的店里的
15 movie posters, oh man. There's a lot of good stuff.
15张电影海报，天哪，一定有很多好东西。
Goonies, Protocol, Beverly Hills, Pee Wee, Cobra, Gremlins,
傻瓜，协议，比佛利山庄，小便，眼镜蛇，小妖精，
注：机翻搞笑时间:-P
man, this is good stuff.
他们确实是好电影
But why no photos?
但是为什么就一张照片？
Ah, here we go.
来，继续
This is an increasingly common sight at Goodwills
这在Goodwill里越来越普遍
in-person and online, but yeah.
无论是线上还是线下，来看看这
Five different Wii consoles and crap load of remotes,
五个不同的Wii主机和大量的遥控器
and Wii condoms and cables, and look all these things.
Wii保护套和电缆，好家伙了
Oof.
emmm.....
Are they degrading on the bottom like this?
他们是这样处理机器的底部的？
Is that starting to happen?
难道就这样开始老化了吗？
I guess it'd be about right. 14, 13 years.
我想应该是这样的吧，十三四年过去了
Yeah, happens with a lot of different rubber feet.
是的，很多橡胶脚上都老化了
Ooh, here we go.
来，咱们继续
This grabs my attention just because of this box
仅仅是盒子就吸引了我的注意
I haven't seen since I was a kid.
我小时候看见过
Seeing this at Toys "R" Us.
在Toys ’R‘ Us店里看见的
Donkey Kong Country box.
Donkey Kong Country box
It was like seriously the entire reason
看上去就是因为这个，他们才买了个任天堂
bought a super Nintendo.
Here's another thing being listed as IOB.
这是被列为IOB的另一件事
This is an Atari 800XL.
这是Atari 800XL
This looks pretty good too overall, wow.
总体来说，品相还不错
It's a low serial number too, look at that.
这也是一个序列号比较小的，看看吧
782? Is that right?
782，是这样吧？
I don't know. 782 473.
我不知道......782473
But anyway, that's a lovely little computer.
但是无论如何，确是一台十分耐人的小电脑呢
Oh, heck yeah. Take a look at this turntable.
Mmm~看看这个唱机
Onkyo CP-1057F Automatic Turntable.
Onkyo CP-1057F自动唱机
Just drawn to it because of that remote,
只是因为那个遥控器而被吸引
I hope there's a photo of the remote.
我希望有遥控器的照片
Little AT cartridge on there.
里面有个AT唱针
Come on, show me the remote. There it is.
来吧，告诉我遥控器在那里
Look at that.
好好欣赏欣赏
Don't see too many automatic turntables with
看不到太多的自动唱机
remotes like this.
附带这样的遥控器
At least I haven't seen too many. That's awesome.
至少我目前没有看到太多，针不戳
Powers on, disc spins, nothing else tested.
能开机，能转动唱片，也没啥了
Well, I don't know. I've already got some cool turntables.
好吧，谁知道呢，我已经有了一些很酷的唱机
I just like the remote, man.
我只是喜欢遥控器
That remote's awesome.
那个遥控器很棒
Well, here's a rather new thing for a Goodwill find.
好吧，这是我在Goodwill里看到的一个新玩意
We've got a Sony Alpha A 6000.
这是个Sony Alpha A 6000
That camera's only a few years old, right?
那台相机刚出来没几年，对吧？
At least at this point.
至少对于目前来说
Okay, battery compartment lock is broken,
好吧，电池仓锁坏了:-(
does not stay closed.
电池盖锁不上
Other than that, I mean what in the world?
除此之外，还有什么呢
It's pretty awesome, can't be too hard of a fix.
非常棒，修复起来不难
Ah man, anybody remember the Bose wave?
啊，伙计，有人记得Bose Wave吗
Remember seeing like commercials and ads for this?
还记得他们的广告吗？
Made it look all amazing.
品相不错
I don't know if it actually sounded as great
我不知道这个东西的音质如何
as it was supposed to have,
像不像当时宣传的那样
but I always kinda wanted to grab one and try out anyway,
但我一直都想搞来一个并体验一下
just because, you know, the wave.
只是因为，这是Wave牌的
That beige plastic, I don't know.
那米色的塑料，额
There's something oddly appealing about it still.
对我而言还挺吸引人的呢
Well, this one got my attention just because of the price
好吧，我只是看到了价格就打开了
and I mean, kind of because of what it is too,
你懂的，就是这么奇怪
but the price.
但这个价格有点......
Two Zippo lighters, just two, but $142 already?
两个Zippo打火机，两个就卖142美元？
Are these really that valuable?
真的值得卖那么多钱吗？
注：是啊，一张《月之暗影》90年代生产的CD卖200块就离谱
That's a pretty neat design, I got to say.
我必须说，这个看上去十分简洁
Not like $142 neat.
简单得不像是142美元的商品
Oh wow, check out the design on this guitar.
天啊，看看这把吉他的设计
I got a Zakk Wylde Les Paul.
这是个Zakk Wylde Les Paul
That is one very loud guitar in more ways than one, I guess.
我猜，这是一把声音很大的吉他
But yeah, seriously, that whole paint job,
但是，这个上色上的是真的很有水平啊:-P
it's a thing right there.
就像这样
You gotta be into it.
你绝对会喜欢的
Hey, I don't see these terribly often.
嗯，我很少看到这些
I mean, they're not super uncommon, but still.
我的意思是，它们虽然没有那么少见，但还是值点钱的
I got some TIMEX Sinclair 1000s here.
这些是TIMEX Sinclair 1000
It's got a memory pack stuck on the back there.
它的背面贴有一个存储包
Bunch of tapes.
一堆磁带
It's not a bad little lot.
品相还没有那么差
I mean, it's not the greatest of computers.
当然，这不是最出色的计算机
I've got one, it's a thing.
我自己就有一台
That's fun for someone.
也许对某些垃圾佬会很有吸引力
Not really finding that many big box PC games,
不幸的是，我最近没有找过那么多的盒装PC游戏
unfortunately, but here's one listed
但我在体育收藏品栏目下看到了一个
under the sports collectibles.
1996's NASCAR Racing.
1996年发行的 NASCAR Racing
Eh, yeah, you know, nothing special but
没错，没什么特别的
like one of the few big boxes I've come across.
跟我看到的那些盒装游戏没什么区别
They had this listed as vintage computer software,
他们将此标注为五款古董电脑软件
five pieces but, I mean, kind of?
是这样吧
A couple of them are just the CD Stomper labeling system.
其中有一些只是CD Stomper标签系统
These are just refills.
还是重新包装好的
I guess there's some software in here, but I mean,
我想这里有一些软件
yeah, I get a Home Designer, Pinnacle Studio,
这是Pinnacle Studio发行的家庭设计师
Roxio Creator.
Roxio Creater
Eh, not interested.
我对此没兴趣
Here we go.
来看看
A nice little TRS-80 over here,
品相不错的TRS-80
is a color computer from 1980
这是台1980年生产的彩色计算机
and it looks pretty good, all things considered.
不挑剔的话，它看起来还不错
And apparently, ooh, it comes with chess.
显然，它是附带国际象棋卡带的
Yeah, I mean, look at that.
没错，看看这个
You got the no real wear where the wrists would go on here,
你没有看到那些为手腕预留的地方
that's normally pretty worn down.
这样打字会很累的
Seems to be an extended basic model as well,
似乎也是基本模型的扩展
so it's been upgraded just a tad.
所以这台电脑已经升级了
Can't tell from here what kind of memory it has,
从这里无法分辨出它里面装着什么类型的内存
maybe 16K but yeah, neat little computer.
也许是16K，但是呢，小机器还挺耐人的呢:-)
I like these.
我喜欢这些东西
What the heck is this?
这又是个嘛？
Milton Bradley MBX Expansion System for TI Home Computer.
适用于TI家用计算机的Milton Bradley MBX扩展系统
Now you can enhance your computer with these
现在，您可以使用这些令人兴奋的功能来增强你的计算机
exciting features:
voice recognition, speech synth, action input,
语音识别，语音合成，动作输入
keypad, analog, joystick.
键盘，模拟，操纵杆
Wow, look at all these things.
哇，看看这堆玩意
And that weird joystick, that tablet-looking deal.
那个怪异的操纵杆，那台平板电脑般的输入板
That's the first for me.
我还是第一次看到这个
Eh, I got a neat little clock radio here.
嗯，我看到这个整洁的小闹钟收音机
1946, apparently.
显然是在1946年生产的
General Electric, just a little Bakelite deal.
通用电气牌的。还是胶木做的棕色外壳呢
Brown.
Yeah, I approve.
没错，是这样的
We got something here still in its box.
这个东西还没开封呢
Sharp RD-600, apparently.
显然是台夏普RD-600
Look at that tape recorder, those piano key controls, man.
看看那台录音机，那些钢琴键样子的控制键
That's got a neat look to it.
看起来很整洁
That's older than any of them I've used.
这台机器比我用过的任何一个磁带机都要老
I kind of like that.
我有点喜欢
Hmm, 8.95. Tempting.
嗯，8.95美元。挺吸引人的
Now look at this Star Trekky-looking thing.
现在来看一下看起来像《星际迷航》的东西
At least with that, you know, logo right there,
至少那上面有徽标
I got an admirable radio receiver here.
这是台令人钦佩的收音机
It's a metal kind of design, coated in something leathery?
这是一种金属设计，表面涂有皮革？
But yeah, look at that antenna.
没错，看看那根天线
Again though, the Trek-like insignia,
还有那个像《星际迷航》的徽章
was that Admiral's thing.
那是Admiral的标志
I haven't seen enough Admiral things to know.
我还没有看过很多关于的Admiral的事情
Oh, what in the 1960s?
这是1960年代生产的什么东西？
This Janica Mini sterero, Jewel Box Radio.
这是Janica Mini双声道珠宝盒收音机
Look at this thing.
看看这个玩意
Look at this thing!
再看看
I like it.
我喜欢
I guess it's just a little jewelry box, but
我想这只是一个小首饰盒，但是
battery powered radio inside.
内置以电池供电的收音机
That's pretty neat.
挺好
Oh man, now that is a clothes iron.
好的，这个是熨斗
I feel like that would just iron through the world
我觉得那只是个大铁疙瘩
if you let it.
如果你那么认为的话
Look at that thing.
看那个东西。
Just wood and metal. That's it.
只是木头和金属而已
Oh, heck yeah, car phone.
好的，这是个车载电话
Or maybe just a cell phone in a bag.
也许只是放在包里的手机
But anyway, these don't get enough love.
但无论如何，他们没有被保养得很好
And this one doesn't have any bids,
而且这个没有任何出价
that's not really surprising.
这并不奇怪
You can't really even use these at all, right?
您甚至根本无法使用它们，对不对？
Like could you rig it up to be used
也许你可以将其装起来
on a modern cell network?
然后在现代网络上用
I don't know, but I like them,
谁知道呢，但是我喜欢他们
especially when they have a bag.
特别是当他们有一个袋子装好的时候
Hello, chrominess and plastic.
向镀铬和塑料产品问好
Sears Counter Craft Toaster Oven.
西尔斯柜台工艺烤面包机及烤箱
That is nasty.
里面真是恶心
It's really nasty.
恶心至极
But, you know, the chromed-out aesthetic with the plastics,
但是，这可是有塑料和镀铬的呢
oh and the worst wood grain.
哦，还有最糟糕的木纹
Hideously beautiful.
真是挺耐人的呢:-P
What the heck is this?
这到底是什么？
Argus Automatic Slide Changer.
阿格斯自动换片机
I thought it was like a stereo setup at first.
起初我以为是立体声设置
Well, this is an alternative to the carousel
好吧，这是我没见过的轮播机的替代品
that I have not seen.
Check it out.
来仔细看看
Hey, that's neat.
嗯，很整洁
I'd kind of like to see that in action
我很想看看运行时的状况
or hear that in action.
听听实际运行时的声音
I bet it sounds awesome.
我敢打赌，这听起来将会很棒
Like chunka, chunka, swapping out slides.
刷刷地，一张张放出幻灯片
I can hear it in my brain.
我能在大脑中想到是怎样
Ooh, Atari computer cassettes.
雅达利电脑磁带
Let's see what is in here.
让我们看看这里有什么
Spelling teacher, math tutor, okay.
拼写老师，数学老师，好吧
Atari, that is a kind of logo from them
Atari，这是他们的一种标志
I've never seen before.
我从没见过
Addition, Word Search, Plumbous?
加法，单词搜索，铅锤？
What?
这是啥？
"The Crypts of Plumbous."
《美洲狮地穴》
Never heard of that one.
从来没有听说过那个
So here's something I wasn't quite understanding
所以这是我不太了解的东西，而这吸引了我
the appeal of at first.
I saw 13 bids, I'm like, "Why? It's just a bunny."
我看到了13个出价，我想：“为什么？这只是一个兔子啊。”
But no, Fenton Satin Vaseline Glass Bunny.
好吧，这是芬顿缎面凡士林玻璃兔子
So it glows green under UV light because it's radioactive.
它会在紫外线下会发出绿色光，因为它具有放射性
This is also known as uranium glass.
这也被称为铀玻璃
I've seen what I think are some of these
我认为我看过其中的一些
out in the wild before at different Goodwills,
在别的线下GoodWill店中
but this one is just confirmed as being that Vaseline glass.
但这只是被证实是凡士林玻璃
That is the fact that it glows green is radioactive,
那是它发出绿色光芒的原因
I love it.
真是耐人啊:-)
Oh, see, now I'm just searching like
好的，现在我正在搜索
Vaseline and radioactive uranium glass on here.
凡士林和放射性铀玻璃
There's all sorts of things popping up.
然后各种各样的事情就突然出现了
Check it out.
来看看
It glows.
它发光
Hey, anybody need some soap?
嘿，有人需要肥皂吗？
Just a bottle of soap and some cream?
只是一瓶肥皂和一些奶油？
Goodwill, 14.99.
在Goodwill卖14.99美元
But it now?
这个呢？
They have buy it nows now? Okay
他们现在有买吗？好吧
Can tell I haven't been on here in a while.
可以说我已经有一段时间没有来过这了
I'm discovering there are an absolute crap load
我发现这里有很多玩意
of perfumes and soaps, makeup sets
有香水和肥皂，还有化妆品套装
and things you don't normally see in the store.
以及通常在商店中看不到的东西
Or if you do, they're, you know,
或者，如果您这样做，他们就
a rather limited selection.
只有这些东西了
Hey, look at this.
嘿，看看这个
It's just bottles of things, man.
只是瓶液体
Look used partially.
看起来已经有人用过了
Are those the samplers? I can't tell.
这是那些采样器吗？我不知道
This whole bath and body personal care section,
这个是洗浴和身体个人护理套装的一部分
all sorts of stuff.
各种各样的东西
BUy some hearing aids from Goodwill.
Goodwill还卖一些助听器
Does that make sense?
还能用吗？
Ooh, what is this? I like the case.
哦，这是什么？我喜欢这个箱子
Brother Valiant Typewriter.
兄弟牌英勇打字机
Oh yeah. Look at that.
看看这个
That is a gorgeous piece of hardware.
真是一块华丽的机器呢
Only familiar with their like 90s word processors.
只是喜欢他们在90年代生产的文字处理器
You know, like this, just typewriters.
你知道，就像打字机一样
uninspiring to an extreme.
令人怀旧的老塑料玩意
Plastic junk.
Whoa, what is this?
哇，这是什么？
Vintage Indiana wooden cash drawer.
老式的印第安纳木制现金抽屉
Wooden, you say?
这是木头做的？
Yeah, I see that.
是的，确实是
Oh.
好吧
Dang, I want to stick my cash in there.
行吧，我想把现金存在那里
And yes, Goodwill has an automotive section.
是的，Goodwill有一个汽车栏目
Goodwill does take cars.
你在Goodwill上确实可以买汽车
You want a 1997 Ford ranger?
您想要1997年的福特游骑兵吗？
The reserve's already been met.
储备金已经满足（ 没看懂:-( ）
It's not a bad little truck.
这卡车还行，不差
Imagine rolling up in your new Mercedes and being like,
想象一下，当你开这辆新梅赛德斯轿车时
"Oh, where'd you get that?"
大家会问：“天哪，你从哪儿买到的？”
"Uh, I got it from Goodwill."
“哦，我是从Goodwill那里买到的。”
Thrift store bins,
二手痕迹十分明显
and a little bit of rust and grime and grossness.
还有点锈蚀，污垢和粗糙感
It's okay, it's a thrift store find.
没关系，这是在一家旧货店里找到的
Check that out.
来看看
Classic Pyrex bowls and glassware kind of things.
经典的耐热玻璃碗和玻璃器皿之类的东西
The memories of like eating off of things with this design.
用这些饭盒吃东西的记忆
Heck, I've still got some,
好吧，又浮现了
some dishware that has that on it, but
上面有一些餐具，但是
I don't know, I think this makes Sunday afternoon lunches
我不知道，我想这是星期天的下午茶
taste better, man.
味道更好
Dinner tastes better out of a Pyrex.
晚餐在耐热玻璃中味道更好
Ah, here we go.
来，咱们继续
I've got a LaserDisc player, a CLD-M301 by Pioneer.
这是台LaserDisc播放器，Pioneer的CLD-M301
Not only that, but it is also a CD changer.
不仅如此，它还是CD换碟机
Let's see here, does it show the mechanism?
让我们看看这里，它显示了里面的机械结构了吗
No, it does not.
好吧，并没有
It says it powers on, the disc tray ejects and retracts.
mao'shu电源打开，光盘托盘可以弹出并缩回
Could not test it more than that.
但无法进行更多测试
Well, you could have shown the tray at least.
好吧，您至少可以显示出托盘
Oh well.
好吧
Oh.
我
我 的
Oh no.
我 的 天
我 的 天 啊
This is...
这有点......
That's a straightforward title, all right.
标题说的倒是明白，好吧
It's a lot of creepy dolls.
有很多令人毛骨悚然的偶。
My goodness.
我的天啊
What?
什么？
You know, that one especially.
你知道，特别是这个
Um...
EW:-(
Yeah, okay.
好吧，吾头在否？
Ooh, what do we have here?
哦，这些是什么呢？
I got some Sega console and accessories, working apparently.
这是些一些世嘉游戏机和配件，显然可以正常工作
$221 at the moment is what the bids are up to.
目前的最高出价是221美元
Yeah, it's a Dreamcast, a few game gears,
是的，这是一个Dreamcast，还有一些游戏装备
a couple of Model 2 Genesises.
几台 Model 2 Genesis
Yeah, all kinds of things in there.
没错，里面有各种各样的东西
I wonder if this was all donated by the same person
我想知道这些是否都是同一个人捐赠的
or just a collection of stuff they got at the same Goodwill.
或者只是他们在同一家Goodwill得到的东西的集合
You never know, but that's a lot of Sega in one spot.
您永远不会知道，但是很多地方都有世嘉
Oh dude, I really like these.
天啊，我真的很喜欢这些
Vintage Durham Appliance Tchotchkes.
达勒姆老式电器小摆件
Yeah, these are actually made by Durham Industrial,
是的，这些实际上是由达勒姆工业公司制造的
If I recall.
如果我记得的话
I've seen these in different antique stores before,
我以前在不同的古董店里看到过这些
they're just like little miniature metal thingies.
它们就是微型的金属小东西
Yeah, there we go. Durham Industries.
再来看看，达勒姆工业公司
They're not necessarily antiques,
他们不一定是古董
but they look like antiques.
但它们看起来像古董
They're made to look like that.
他们看起来像......
I don't know.
怎么说呢
I just like miniature type of things and these are nifty.
我只是很喜欢这些微型的小玩意，这些都很耐人
Hey, check it out.
来看看
We got a boxed Creative Sound Blaster Live sound card here.
这是个盒装的Creative Sound Blaster Live声卡
The Best Buy open items sticker's been marked out, but yeah.
上面标着百思买未清项目标签
Don't run across the original live in the box too often.
我不会经常在包装盒中看到原始的标签
What's that going for? 36 at the moment, four bids.
接着看......目前有36个竞标价格
Curious what that'll end up selling for.
我很好奇最终会卖出多少钱
And lastly, oh my goodness.
最后，我的天哪
Check this out.
看一下这个
We got a Voodoo3 3500 TV AGP video card
这是个Voodoo3 3500 TV AGP视频卡
complete in the box.
完整的盒装
Not only that, but it is sealed in the box.
不仅如此，它还被密封在盒子里
Oof, I'm sure this is going to go for a good bit.
嗯，我确定网上一直会有这个
These can go for a few hundred, at least,
标价都在几百美元
on eBay from what I've seen.
至少eBay上是这样的
I've tried to get a 3500 in the box before,
我曾经想买一个盒装的Voodoo3 3500显卡
and so far, I've been outbid.
到目前为止，我的出价一直很高
Looks like that was removed potentially for a rebate,
看起来该商品已被删除，有可能会有折扣
but yeah, and...
但是呢，我要参与进去，我要出价
I'm going to ahead and put in a bid here.
Let's see.
我们来看看
300 seems fair,
300美元似乎很合适
I'm sure I'll get outbid but...
我敢肯定我会胜出，但是.呢
Well actually, how long is left?
好吧，离竞价结束还有多久？
We got 101, eight hours left.
我们出了101美元，还有八个小时。
Alrighty, well I've put in my bid.
好吧，我已经出价了
Doink.
好的
Yay.
:-O
So that put it up to 126,
现在已经126美元了
that was the previous max bid.
那是之前的最高出价
Mine is higher than that, of course.
我的出价当然比这更高
We'll see what happens when I come back in eight hours.
我们将在八小时后回来，看看会发生什么
Alrighty, it is late in the evening here
好了，现在是深夜
and the auction is over and check it out.
拍卖结束了，来看看
I won.
我赢了:-)
It wasn't exactly cheap, but you know,
这并不便宜，但你知道
considering what it is, $257 is not a terrible price to pay
考虑到是这个东西，对于这个盒装密封的的Voodoo3 3500显卡来说
for a 3500 sealed in the box.
257美元不是一个很高的价钱
Like I said, the last one I saw sell in this condition
我刚说到，上回我在ebay上看到这个品相的
on eBay was over 300 and
没拆封的标价是多于300美元的
the most recent one to sell in the box,
just an open box, not sealed,
还有一个在敞开盒子里，没密封的
that was $220 on eBay.
在eBay上卖是220美元
So, you know, 257 for a brand new
因此，你现在知道257美元
in the box, never been opened, I am cool with that
买来一个盒装没拆封的显卡，就挺好B-)
so let's go ahead and pay for it.
好的，让我们继续付款
And then yeah, that's that,
然后，就是这样
it's taken care of in terms of being paid for so
在支付方面得到了照顾
it's just up to them to ship it whenever they can here.
只要他们可以往这里运送，他们怎么办都行
Hopefully pretty soon.
希望物流能快些
Of course, I'm not going to be able to show myself
当然，接下来的部分我就
getting it here in this video because
不在视频中放出来了
I'm going to get this video posted,
我要赶紧把这部片子发行
but perhaps I'll do that in the next episode
但也许我会在下一集的
of LGR eThrifts, showing this card arriving.
LGR eThrifts中展示这张运送中的显卡
And yeah, I guess that's it for this episode.
好的，这集就是这样啦
Let me know what you thought about this format,
如果您以后还想看到这种类型的节目的话
if you'd like to see it again in the future.
请你给我提出关于这种视频的建议
And if you have any ideas for
如果你对内容的添加或更改有任何想法的话
what could be added to or changed,
or whatever kind of experiences you've had
或者你曾经有过在Goodwill网站上购物的经历
shopping on the shop Goodwill website,
or maybe some other websites you'd like to see me check out
或者是在其他网站网购的经历的话
in terms of shopping online and such.
I will absolutely be going back thrifting in-person
我绝对会亲自地去看看
whenever it makes sense, but yeah,
只要东西对我有用的话
I'm just not doing that right now.
但是我现在不会这样做
Things are too weird.
形势越来越糟了
But a number of you are still thrifting here and there,
但是，你们中的许多人仍在淘二手
definitely not as much,
绝对没有之前那么多
cause I haven't gotten as many photos as usual,
因为我没有像往常一样收到太多照片
but you're sending in some finds regardless.
但无论如何你们都会跟我分享你们的好运
So yeah, thank you for sending those in.
所以说，谢谢你们发给我你们的发现
It's awesome seeing what you found,
看到你们发现的东西真是太棒了
and hopefully I can join you all once again
希望在将来我能再次加入你们淘二手大军
in the thrift stores out in the wild in the future,
as things continue on their course.
这要视乎事情的发展
But yeah, that's it for this episode of LGR eThrifts.
但是呢，这就是LGR eThrifts第一集的全部内容
Thanks for watching.
感谢大家观看:-)
本片由SuperBart翻译，原作者LGR发布于2020-9-11
希望大家双十一能够好运大爆发，并且钱包没空;-)